like she like the Virgin married and she
was stripping like she was dancing to No
Quarter I woke up from that like I'll
never do heroin again but I'm lying I
did in New York one time in a gay bar up
in the third floor ramrod it you
got to take a chance Columbus did
[Music]
[Applause]
right what welcome to this is not
happening presents one crazy night so
this is what we do a bunch of comedians
uh tell stories about a similar subject
so this is just one crazy night ladies
and gentlemen my friend and yours Mr
Joey Diaz
everybody one more time for har to put
this
together so all messed up you know like
half of the in here have
been all up all right something's
always us up for me it was 30
years of just drugs and and no
JK here we got down all right so
when he called me up and he's like hey I
want you to do the story I did like I I
got high right I smoked a joint right I
and I made like a drug Tombstone right
like like acid you know 79 to like 85
and then I did like quo you know 80 to
87 and you know THC Crystal went and
then you I did blow for a long time
towards the in 2005 I was up and
I really wanted to quit I wanted to quit
at the 25 year mark you follow me but I
just I couldn't do it like once I hit
that Centennial I had to do
something but I had too much pride to go
to a rehab there was a rehab on
Hollywood Boulevard next to rck I went
down there for like a week under an
alias but then they started snooping
around I had to get the out of
there right in the old days you could
push an alias like a after
911 it's tough out there for a b you
know me so it they start that Jose
what you
it's Anonymous
what's with the question sh
so I've done heroin before right like
when I was like 17 I stole this thing
with Dei cantero this little
crazy Cuban kid we stole like this thing
where you put dishes in it was brand new
the people left in front of the people's
houses me and Diddy picked it up and
walked five blocks to gun to Brown's
house if you ask me again I'll knock you
down right this guy he was like
the neighborhood lone shark like if you
stole something he'd buy it from me so I
go over there and I'm like you know I
want to sell you this he's like you drop
it off and come back in 2 hours you look
like Tony iomi the guitar player from
Black Sabbath and he always Ed the door
with a robe with his underwear showing
like the dude in Boogie Nights
he was he was he was creepy but not
really you know what I'm saying like you
had to take a chance with this
Right Said goes come back in 2 hours I
go in there we're rocking we're talking
right he goes I got you $60 s he's
like hang out man I want to do business
and hang out with you you seem like a
cool dude so I'm sitting there he's like
you want to do some heroin at the time I
had done everything right like uh you
know Coke I had done like uh tomol I had
done like THC Crystal AKA Gorilla
Biscuits AKA elephant
tranquilizes so I'm like it if you
want at this time I was a up kid
you know I had no direction I said
it I'll do the heroin right and I did
this gagger this white Chinese
heroin I heard like Chinese music in the
background
D I do this thing all a sudden it's like
the room start spinning and I
got a puke and I puke and I and I pass
out and I think I'm dead but I heard
like No Quarter by Jimmy PA the live
live from the garden and that's how
I knew I was alive so I got up on my
hands and knees and I sat with the puke
on my face and Jimmy was
blasting at the 5 minute Mark if you
listen to that uh The Song Remains the
Same Jimmy Paige drops it like a
Soldier especially when you're
on heroin you get the tingles up and
down your back right and it was on I
felt that heroin the warmth from God
like that's what it is your balls are
warm you want to come but it don't
matter you know what I'm saying like you
want to come but it it wouldn't be
good enough as the warmth you're feeling
in your body my ears and I could see all
these like I wasn't hallucinating but it
was so warm I was feeling like I seen
every woman that I ever seen in my life
and make contact with not sex I was too
young for that like I seen the lunch
lady there Mr SA
know I seen the lady who gave me birth
do you follow me who smacked me in the
ass I seen the nun who I tackled
in the fourth grade I seen all these
in this dream I seen my
mother then I seen like the Virgin mared
and that's when I knew I was up
and she was stripping like she was
dancing to No Quarter and that's
up right there right and I had already
made my confirmation I was up
right there I was I was frur as a
Catholic already at that age
right so that was it when I woke up from
that sh I go I'll never do heroin again
but I'm lying I did it again in the
halfway house in '94 right and I did in
New York one time at a gay bar up in the
third floor ram rod that's what you do
when you're up there it you got to
take a chance Columbus did right got to
do heroin out of gay bar it that's
how you know and you over there
dancing looking at the gay dudes and
driving them bananas and
anyway so it's 2005 I'm living in
Hollywood and I'm doing a
grandma blow and I sometimes was like a
bad night by 8:00 every night I'd be
watching TV and I get this pain in my
soul and I get my bones would
hurt I I couldn't hear the TV like I
wanted to watch something on TV and I
couldn't and I get in my car and I take
the ATM I lived on shra I go all the way
to Sunset and Hollywood Rouse
rock and roll Rous is an ATM right there
and I swear in my mother's grave
I wouldn't stop for a red light I didn't
give a I didn't give a I
parked right in front of it put my
hazard lights on it like a doctor i
r without a handicap stick I don't give
a I take out 60 bucks and right
there I call a drug deal I had a couple
of them the Armenian only came out the
weekends the black guy was there every
night and the Mexican was
there like four nights a week depending
what shift he was working so I I knew
all their shifts and so I would go
buy a gram go home do it in the
garage go upstairs make believe I was
and jerk off in the bathroom
and look out the window that was
the extent of my addiction at
the time then at 2:00 when it wear off
I'd called another drug dealer and so
they wouldn't know my addiction
right now was I going to go to a
rehab no so I'm talking to a buddy
of mine one day after 911 he moved back
to Newark I go say you're living with
your mother he's like 40 something I go
so do you still do heroin he goes like
you every night he goes I cop down
in new Yark I cop $7 bags of heroin I go
send me a
couple now you ever have a conversation
with somebody and then you're like you
just try to be cool you're like yeah
Count Me In wrong dude
right about a week later I go to my
mailbox looks like in Crayola writing
you
know like Joey Coco he spelled Coco
wrong with 2K and Diaz right I'm
like what the no return address
right I take it upstairs I open it and
there they are three little bags
of H white that Chinese that the
terrorists are bringing in like a
by the day load with a
picture on Obama on it balls ass naked
smoking a joint and with a white
chick Ling his nuts like a
doctor
right so I'm like it so I'm I'm
doing the blurry night so this Monday
night I go it tonight's a different
night I'm doing like a little line his H
and I usually what I would do I was
crazy my girlfriend's great she
don't get high so I would trick I go you
got to go to bed dog you got to get
eight
hours you're at that age you need every
don't worry about me I'm a
comedian this what I do you got
to go to bed right now but while all
this is going on there was a cat
population growing in my backyard
and I had already adopted three of these
little right and they had
the problem was they had two they had
the mama who was a dirty then they
had two big cats that was slinging dick
like you know they had the Siamese the
War I call him the samurai he had big
black balls and he was Siamese I'm not
kidding you when he'd walk he'd walk all
up like this guy meant it
never talked to me N9 years never took a
lobster nothing he was a soldier he just
star me down you you ain't
buying my love all
right then there was a black and white
one who was a big cat and they were both
masama so she kept having
kittens and then they would kill the
kittens so she would stop ovulating and
get back to this is how serious
these cats were right now
how did I learn about this you know I
did some reading on the internet when
you're doing coke you stay up late
night and you do investigating you
follow me so uh she had the kittens and
they were beautiful they were three
Siamese kittens and there's one black
and white dirty right but
the three Siamese there two girls and a
boy DJ DJ was the best little cat in the
world they lived outside and I step out
in my backyard and I go DJ and he come
running like a superhero and the
two little curs would come and then that
super bad this little black and white
would come and I they would all hang out
around me but super bad the black and
white one would take DJ and take them up
trees and and take them off the
territory would take them on Salma by
the YMCA I have to get super bad what
days I'm going to kill you
cocksuck all right and I caught myself
even though I love the cats I would
never put a hit on a cat but in my mind
I'm like I'm going to kill this
little cat right seriously and I
love cats don't get me wrong but you
know those cats that just get on your
last neres you don't know how to
do it but you love animals too much so
you know you're just bullshitting
yourself so I like one day he's just
going to get hit by a truck or something
that little sucker don't
hang with him no more DJ and I was just
waiting to bring DJ upstairs and I had a
a chick that was going to take the two
sies and then super bad I didn't
know what the hell was going to happen
to super bad right so my addiction's
getting worse wor and one night I get
home my my wife is at the time
was my girlfriend she's crying like the
cats outside they're going to
die what the what are you talking about
so we got the two girls we brought them
to the vet and she adopted them out
through Petco and then I go what are you
going to do with super bad that
mut and VJ my baby and she goes well I'm
going to bring him up and I go leave
super bad outside just leave him the
outside that's how much I hated
super
bad so I go out one night and my rule
was people this is how up in my
addicted mind my rule was never to do
Coke in the house cuz was was bad
luck I would always do it in the car so
by the time I got upstairs I had a
and i' run into the bathroom and hide
you follow me that was the plan
I had a plan I was an organized cocaine
type of right so this night
something happened I had to go to the
bathroom I didn't have time I ran
upstairs and when I get upstairs my wife
goes in the bathroom the two cats are in
the bathroom so I go in the bathroom and
I I I do the Coke and I'm looking at the
boat of them I'm like I don't even know
why she brought you up here and
I go back outside and I do the Coke and
I probably got some more I don't know
how f story and I went to bed and when I
got up my wife woke me up in the middle
of night she goes hey I just want to
tell you that DJ died and that
was the sign me I was going to adopt
right and I when she said it guys I
knew it was the coke I
knew it and I just said do me a favor
close the door and I cried a little bit
and I put the pillow put my sleep atne a
mask on first then I went to bed
right yeah whatever sleep at me or
whatever the it is I'm a fat dude
right and then so I'm laying there
thinking I finish my crying I go you
know what that little cat died because I
brought the coke upstairs even if I
hate super bad that
is not going to die up here cuz that's
even more bad luck so I went in there I
got on my hands and knees like a
Catholic Soldier and I said God
if you save these cat is super
bad I can't stand I'll never do Coke
again I like winked at him like right
whatever I said God don't let this
die and I promise you and
like the first day I had the
you know but every day I would go in the
bathroom and he'd live like by the
fourth day I was ready to shoot
myself I was ready just to shoot him and
ended I would go there like die don't
you feel like dying
yet it's over you don't want to live
it's terrible things are tough
out there trust me that was seven years
ago and I haven't done blow I tell you
what I'll tell you how close I am with
this filthy that I love cuz
if you go to my house and you look at my
cats and you look at him you're
like he's like Maryland on the monsters
you follow him
I got goodlooking siameses and he's like
black and white and got a little head
and but he's feeless I tell you how
much that dude knew I made a promise
from because at night my other cats are
cool but they ain't that cool
but at night when I go in to my bedroom
I take my slippers off I put my sleep
atne mask on I put the fan on and I lay
down and I pick the blanket up and I go
super bad and wherever the this
is you hear like boom you
hear him hit the door and he jumps next
to me and I put the blanket over him and
that's the end of the night he's
still there stay black thank
God Sophia one more time putting this
together
[Applause]
tonight hey why don't you click like so
that this YouTube clip gets better views
And subscribe so you can see next week
story and don't forget to leave a
comment I command
[Music]
you